athousandcountryroads.com 2018-07-28

# Privacy Policy - A Thousand Country Roads

## **A Thousand Country Roads Privacy Policy & Disclosure**

This blog is a personal blog written and edited by us, Harry and Lynndee. This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, or other forms of compensation.

This blog abides by word of mouth marketing standards. We believe in honesty of relationship, opinion and identity. The compensation received may influence the advertising content, topics or posts made in this blog. That content, advertising space or post will be clearly identified as paid or sponsored content.

The owners of this blog are compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owners of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

This blog does not contain any content which might present a conflict of interest.

## **Cookies**

This blog does not share personal information with third parties nor do we store any information about your visit to this blog other than to analyze and optimize your content and reading experience through the use of cookies. You can turn off the use of cookies at anytime by changing your specific browser settings.

## **Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site, we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

## **Analytics**

This website uses Google Analytics to track website traffic. But all the data collected is processed in a way that visitors will not be identified.

## **How Long We Retain Your Data**

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

## **Where We Send Your Data**

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## **Plugin: Smush**

Smush sends images to the WPMU DEV servers to optimize them for web use. This includes the transfer of EXIF data. The EXIF data will either be stripped or returned as it is. It is not stored on the WPMU DEV servers.

Smush uses a third-party email service (Drip) to send informational emails to the site administrator. The administrator’s email address is sent to Drip and a cookie is set by the service. Only administrator information is collected by Drip.

## **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is subject to change without notice. The most recent version of the privacy policy will always be posted on this site. This privacy policy was last updated on May 28, 2018.

## **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions feel free to contact us directly at athousandcountryroads@gmail.com.
